news-pr.in 2017-12-19

# Privacy Policy | NewsPR

### Privacy Policy

At News-PR.in, we are dedicated to protecting your privacy. The information collected about you is used to process orders and to create a more personalized shopping experience. What information is collected? How do we use the information we collect? When you order, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card number, and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to contact you of your order status – for example through a confirmation notice.

We also collect e-mail addresses at various locations within the website, including when you order from the website so that we can send you any necessary e-mail messages related to your order. We monitor customer traffic patterns and website usage to help us develop the design and layout of our online store and the products and services we offer. We do not share credit card information with third parties except for the purpose of processing payments for products you’ve ordered and as required by law of the Indian Government.

How do we keep your customer information safe? When you place orders or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. If at any time you would like us to delete any of your personal information on file, just e-mail , our customer service.

As you browse News-PR.in, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in.  If however, you’d prefer not to receive relevant banner advertisements, you can visit this page to opt at any time.

We are devoted to protecting your privacy. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. By using this website you consent to the collection and use of the information you provide to News-PR and its affiliates.

**External Links  **

This site contains links to other sites. NewsPR is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us.
